http://www.paperthermometer.com/pages/privacy-policy

Call Us Toll Free 877-785-2235My AccountFollow Us: Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Shop Product Lines 1-Temp Thermolabel®3-Temp Thermolabel®5-Temp Thermolabel®5-Temp Classic Thermolabel®8-Temp Thermolabel®8-Temp Classic Thermolabel®Thermopaper®MiscellaneousCustom ProductsShop Industry Shop All IndustriesManufacturingGeneral ManufacturingTextilesScreen PrintingMetal CoatingCabinets & FurnitureFood & Beverage ProductionFood ServiceResearchAbout Our CompanyBlogHistoryWhy ThermolabelCustomer Service Request A SampleProduct UseContact UsTechnical InformationOrdering InformationInternational Ordering
Close MenuShop Product Lines 1-Temp Thermolabel®3-Temp Thermolabel®5-Temp Thermolabel®5-Temp Classic Thermolabel®8-Temp Thermolabel®8-Temp Classic Thermolabel®Thermopaper®MiscellaneousCustom ProductsShop Industry Shop All IndustriesManufacturingGeneral ManufacturingTextilesScreen PrintingMetal CoatingCabinets & FurnitureFood & Beverage ProductionFood ServiceResearchAbout Our CompanyBlogHistoryWhy ThermolabelCustomer Service Request A SampleProduct UseContact UsTechnical InformationOrdering InformationInternational Ordering
Home
|
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The following is the Online Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) of Paper Thermometer Co., Inc. (the “Company”). The Company collects information from you when you use the Company’s website, www.paperthermometer.com (the “Website”). By using the Website, you consent to the terms of this Policy.When ordering products from the Website or registering on the Website, you may be asked for personal information including without limitation your name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card number (“Personal Information”). You may, however, visit the Website anonymously if you do not place an order through the Website.
Your credit card information is only used in connection with the processing of your product orders. Any other Personal Information that the Company collects from you may be used in one or more of the following ways: (1) to personalize your experience with the Website to enable the Company to better respond to your needs; (2) to improve the Website based on information and feedback that we receive from you; (3) to administer a contest, promotion, or other feature of the Website; (4) to send periodic marketing materials or other information about the Company or the Company’s products to you; and (5) to respond to your questions and requests.
The Company implements security measures to maintain the security of your Personal Information when you enter, submit, or access your Personal Information. All Personal Information is transmitted via security technology and can be accessed only by authorized personnel who are required to keep Personal Information confidential.
The Company never collects or maintains Personal Information from those it actually knows are under the age of 18. By using the Website, you certify that you are 18 years of age or older. By requesting a sample, or purchasing a product you agree to receive marketing communications from the Company. You may choose to opt-out of these at any time.
The Company does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your Personal Information to third-parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist the Company in operating the Website or in conducting the Company’s business, including the servicing of your product orders, so long as those parties agree to keep your Personal Information confidential. The Company may also release your Personal Information when appropriate or necessary to comply with the law or protect the Company’s rights, property, or safety.
The Company may, from time to time, change the terms of this Policy. All changes to the Policy will be posted on the Website and will be effective when posted.
If there are any questions regarding the Policy, you may contact the Company by writing to us at: Paper Thermometer Company, Inc., 62 Colin Dr, Manchester, NH 03103, or contacting us by telephone at (603) 547-2034 or by email at info@paperthermometer.com.
ErrorWhat are you looking for? SubmitYour cartYou don't have any items in your cart.{property.name}: {property.value} x
Subtotal:
View Cart
